Contact

Kabupaten Cianjur 081575271662 (Mobile) dssetiawan05@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/dedisetiawan-05 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Pengembangan Web

Java

Flutter

Certifications

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Back-End untuk Pemula

Belajar Dasar Pemrograman JavaScript

Belajar Fundamental Front-End Web Development

Belajar Prinsip Pemrograman SOLID

Dedi Setiawan

Full Stack Dev | Software Engineer | Flutter enthusiast Cianjur, West Java, Indonesia

Summary

Experienced Teacher with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry. Skilled in Javascript, PHP, Internet of Things, After Effects, Adobe Premiere Pro, and Cascading Style Sheets (CSS). Strong education professional with a 2013 focused in Computer Software Engineering from SMK Al-ittihad Boarding School.

Experience

PT Wide Technologies Indonesia Frontend Developer February 2022 - Present (10 months) Jakarta Selatan, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

Score Campus
Full Stack Developer
February 2022 - February 2022 (1 month)

SMK Negeri 1 Pacet
Teacher
July 2019 - February 2022 (2 years 8 months)
Cianjur, West Java, Indonesia

SMP IT Hayatan Thayyibah Teacher August 2018 - August 2019 (1 year 1 month) Sukabumi, West Java, Indonesia

Education

Hacktiv8 Indonesia

Full-stack Javascript · (June 2021 - January 2022)

Universitas Sains Al-Qur'an (UNSIQ) Jawa Tengah di Wonosobo Bachelor's degree, Information Technology · (September 2013 - September 2017)

SMK Al-ittihad Boarding School 2013, Computer Software Engineering · (July 2010 - July 2013)